# Hanna Tovsta

# Web Developer

#### SUMMARY

Motivated IT professional with a solid career spanning since 2011. Transitioned into the industry immediately after completing university, gaining valuable experience and knowledge from my initial role. Committed to continuous learning and professional development to stay abreast of the latest industry advancements.

# SKILLS

<ul><li>Aiax</li></ul>	<ul><li>Bootstrap</li></ul>

DOMHTML5

JavaScriptWordPress

• GIT • PHP

CSSMySQL

# **EDUCATION**

 Social Informatics at National Technical University "Kharkiv Polytechnic Institute" 2004-2008

### ADDITIONAL COURSES AND TRAININGS

ENGLISH COURSE at Green Forest - Kharkiv
 https://my.greenforest.com.ua/certificate/f39ceaeb331de9aa0c58c595005d981a13ec0788

• Front-end Basic at Hillel IT School

https://certificate.ithillel.ua/view/66932017 EXCELLENT

• Front-end Pro at Hillel IT School 2023

# WORK EXPERIENCE

Wordpress Developer at iWelt
 Installing multisite projects based on Wordpress Network, maintaining old projects in the company

CMS Developer at **P2H** 2016-2022

~ Creating custom themes and templates for each client based on Wordpress, Joomla, Shopify ~ Maintaining our projects

CMS WEB Developer at W3M Ukraine
 2011-2016

# новву

I'm interested in these areas: ~ Arts and Culture ~ Science and Technology ~ Children and education ~ Animal Welfare ~ Environment

# CONTACTS

#### Location

! Remote only

✓ Will consider relocation

Emai

# tovsta.hanna@gmail.com

Dhone

# +17575801273

Telegram

https://t.me/annatovsta

Linkedli

https://www.linkedin.com/in/hanna-tovsta-40719252/

### LANGUAGES

- English B1
- Ukrainian C1
- Russian C2